* Resources

    Follow Bulc Club[](https://www.twitter.com/bulcclub/ "Follow Bulc Club on Twitter")[](https://www.facebook.com/bulcclub/ "Follow Bulc Club on Facebook")[](https://www.linkedin.com/company/bulc-club "Connect with Bulc Club on LinkedIn")[](https://medium.com/@bulcclub "Follow Bulc Club on Medium")[](https://www.instagram.com/bulcclub "Follow Bulc Club on Instagram")[](https://vimeo.com/bulcclub "Watch Bulc Club Videos on Vimeo")
    
* [FAQs](https://www.bulc.club/faqs "Bulc Club Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)")

### Bulc Club Privacy Policy

Effective 05/23/22

#### Bulc Club's goal is to rid the world of bulkmail. Your email address will never be shared with the public or third parties. **Ever**.

This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information by Bulc Club and ERA404 Creative Group, Inc. ("Bulc Club"). To learn which company is responsible for processing your personal information and for instructions on how to contact us, please see the "International Users/Contacting Us" section below. By using, visiting or browsing the Bulc Club service, you accept and agree to our information practices described below.

Please note that this Privacy Policy include hyperlinks that may be accessed only through our website, so if you are reviewing this Privacy Policy elsewhere, in print or a non-web-friendly device, you may need to visit [bulc.club/legal/privacy](https://www.bulc.club/legal/privacy) to review hyperlinked items.

1. **Collection and Use of Information**
    
    We receive and store information, including personal information, about you and your use of our service. This information is gathered in a number of ways, including when you enter it on our website and from interactions with our service. In this Privacy Policy, we use the term "personal information" to mean information that can be used to uniquely identify or contact you. Non-personal information is information that does not permit direct association with you. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. You can choose not to provide personal information we may request of you, but, in general, most of the personal information we request is required in order to provide our service and the lack of such personal information will prevent us from doing so.
    
    When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts. For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you as well as information from other sources, as permitted by law. We use this personal information for various reasons, including to activate your membership, to provide you with our service, and to communicate on these and other topics. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send notifications about Bulc Club features, changes in service, and other correspondence concerning our service. If you no longer want to receive certain communications from us via email, simply log-in and access the **Notifications** tab in your **Member Console** Settings ([bulc.club/members](https://members.bulc.club/?login)) and uncheck those items to unsubscribe, or click the "unsubscribe" link in the email. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account status.
    
    We keep track of your interactions with us and collect information related to you and your use of our service, including but not limited to: your online activity, Member Ratings, Internet protocol addresses, device and software data (such as type, configuration and unique identifiers), and related activity. We use this information for such purposes as determining your general geographic location, enforcing our terms, personalizing the service and our messaging/language, tracking usage fraud, determining your Internet service provider, helping us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise analyzing, enhancing, or administering our service for you and other users. We provide analysis of our users in the aggregate or otherwise in anonymous form to prospective partners, acquirers, and other third parties. We may disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, usage and demographic information and other information. For example, we use general statistics of usage and emails filtered to monitor the success of our service and attract new members.
    
    While using the Bulc Club service, you will have opportunities to mark email addresses and domains as "bulk mail". Please understand that when you post such information, it is anonymously used to affect Bulc Club Member Ratings for members and the public, and is not subject to this policy. We are not responsible for any third party's use of ratings and the information you publicly disclose through our service. However, your ratings are anonymous and contain no personally identifying information.
    
2. **Disclosure of Personal Information.**
    
    We use other companies, agents or contractors ("Service Providers") to perform services on our behalf or to assist us with the provision of services to you. For example, we engage Services Providers to provide communications, infrastructure and IT services, personalize and optimize our service, provide customer service, and analyze and enhance data, including users' interaction with our service. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your account information. We do not authorize these companies to use or disclose this information except in connection with providing the services we request of them.
    
    Bulc Club also reserves the right to disclose personal information if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, (b) enforce applicable terms of use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Bulc Club, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. In connection with any reorganization, restructuring, merger or sale, or other transferring of assets we reserve the right to transfer information, including personal information, provided that the receiving party agrees to respect your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.
    
3. **Other Websites, Platforms and Applications.**
    
    The Bulc Club service may be provided through platforms or contain links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of information may differ from ours. For example, you may be able to access the Bulc Club service (or application) through platforms such as Google Play or Apple iTunes Store on a number of other Internet connected devices. While we endeavor to associate with reputable companies, Bulc Club cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other websites and platforms. These websites and platforms have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully. In addition, you may encounter third party applications that interact with the Bulc Club service. To learn more about these, see our Terms of Use ([bulc.club/legal/terms/](http://www.bulc.club/legal/terms/)).
    
4. **Children**
    
    You must be 18 years of age or older to subscribe to the Bulc Club service. In certain jurisdictions, the age of majority may be older than 18, in which case, you must satisfy that age in order to become a member. While individuals under the age of 18 may utilize the service, they may do so only with the involvement, supervision, and approval of a parent or legal guardian, and subject to our Terms of Use ([bulc.club/legal/terms/](http://www.bulc.club/legal/terms/)).
    
5. **Right to Access Your Information**
    
    We give you access and the ability to update a broad range of information about your account, including your contact information and your communication preferences in your Member Console. You must be signed in to access your Member Console. If you have a question regarding our privacy practices, or want to exercise your rights regarding your personal information, please contact us through our Member Support page ([bulc.club/contact/](http://www.bulc.club/contact/)).
    
6. **Cookies**
    
    We and our service providers use cookies for various reasons. For example, we use cookies and other technologies to make it easy to access our services by remembering you when you return, to provide and analyze our services, to learn more about our users, and to deliver and tailor new features to our service. We want you to be informed about our use of this technology, so this notice explains the types of technologies we use, what they do and your choices regarding their use.
    
    1. **What are cookies?**
        
        Cookies are small data files that are commonly stored on your device when you browse and use websites and online services. They are widely used to make websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information and assist with service or advertising personalization.
        
    2. **Why does Bulc Club use cookies?**
        
        We and our service providers may use the following types of cookies:
        
        * **Essential cookies:** These cookies are strictly necessary to provide our website or online service. For example, we or our service providers may use these cookies to authenticate and identify our members when they use our websites and applications so we can provide our service to them. They also help us to enforce our Terms of Use, prevent fraud and maintain the security of our service.
        * **Performance and functionality cookies:** These cookies are not essential, but help us to personalize and enhance your online experience with Bulc Club. For example, they help us to remember your preferences and prevent you from needing to re-enter information you previously provided (for example, during member sign up). We also use these cookies to collect information (such as statistics and other information) about our members' use of the Bulc Club service so that we can enhance and personalize our website and service and conduct market research. Deletion of these types of cookies will result in limited functionality of our service.
        * **Personalized advertising cookies:** The public "[Check Ratings](https://www.bulc.club/check/ "Check BULC CLUB Member Rating")" results pages contain advertisments served by Google and third-party vendors. Google's use of advertising cookes enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visits to our site and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads "Google Ads Settings"). Alternately, users can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting: [AboutAds.Info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "AboutAds.info").
    3. **How can I exercise choice regarding cookies and other types of online tracking?**
        
        For more information about cookies set through our website, as well as other types of online tracking (including the collection of information by third parties about your online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services), and to exercise choices regarding them, please contact us through our Member Support page ([bulc.club/contact/](http://www.bulc.club/contact/)). At this time, we do not respond to Web browser "do not track" signals.
        
7. **Security**
    
    Bulc Club takes information security seriously and uses reasonable administrative, technical, physical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. For example, we utilize Secure Sockets Layering, an industry-standard protocol for certain of your transmissions to us, in order to encrypt certain personal information that you send to us through the registration and sign up process.
    
    Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using our service, including our website and user interfaces, or providing information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Bulc Club service.
    
    You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account access information and for restricting access to your computer or device through which you access your Bulc Club account. Where possible, users of public or shared devices should log out at the completion of each visit. If you sell or return a computer or internet-ready device, you should log-out and deactivate the device before doing so. If you do not maintain the security of your password or device, or fail to log out or deactivate your device, subsequent users may be able to access your account, including your personal information.
    
8. **Changes to This Policy**
    
    Bulc Club may, from time to time, make changes to this Privacy Policy. Such revisions shall be effective immediately; provided however, for existing members, such revisions shall, unless otherwise stated, be effective 30 days after posting. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised.
    
9. **Transfer of Information**
    
    Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by using Bulc Club, you acknowledge and agree to the transfer of your information outside your country of residence to any country (including the United States) where we have facilities or engage third parties (including but not limited to payment processors, cloud service or other IT providers, and other companies that provide services to us). You understand that the countries to which we may transfer information may not have as comprehensive a level of data protection as in your country.
    
10. **Contacting Us**
    
    If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy, including the treatment of your personal information and/or our use of cookies and other technologies, please contact us at the following address:
    
    ERA404 Creative Group, Inc.  
    Attn: Bulc Club General Counsel  
    PO Box 470404  
    Brooklyn, NY 11247  
    USA

© Copyright 2024. [ERA404 Creative Group, Inc.](http://www.era404.com/ "ERA404 Creative Group") All rights reserved. Patent Pending.
